All right, these are the 11 players who'll move on to the final stage.
Oichi Fukatsu, Leon Sook, Toi Kachita, Junosuke Nakano, Yudai Hasegawa, Kensho Soda, Mamoru Izumi, Esaku Otomo, Akinori Kanida, Soichiro Tachibana.
Sir!
And last but not least...
Sorry, Shun, can you grab that?
Yeah, sure.
I did it.
I made the final cut, Shun!
Final stage of assessment!
That means I'm almost there!
Way to go!
I still can't believe it!
So close!
You'll ace this test, I know it.
My stakes are high since I taught you how to play.
I'm counting on you to raise my stock.
I'll do my best!
Thanks, Shun.
The final stage will commence in 30 minutes.
Hey! You guys want to chat?
Um, no pressure. I mean, just if you feel like it.
I figured since there are 11 who made the cut,
then that means the final stage is going to be an 11-on-11 match.
So it'll be all of us against another 11, right?
Then, uh, I was thinking that maybe we should get to know each other a little better since we're on a team.
Uh, really?
What's up with you?
It took a lot of courage to stand out here and ask you guys that!
Otomo?
I don't feel like being alone until the final stage starts.
Let's chat.
I'd like to know your thoughts on love, and the origin of the word itself.
Good idea.
And I kind of like you both.
Oh?
Uh, yeah, me too.
Hey, count me in.
All righty, then.
Um, want to play truth or dare?
I just say you wanted to talk when you've got nothing!
Fine.
I'll start it.
Everyone say what your favorite playing style is.
Like, what kind of passes you want to receive.
What's all that?
Not sure, but I'm guessing they are trying to come up with a plan.
That's good.
So, yeah, those are the kind of passes I prefer.
Uh, it's weird how picky you all are.
Look who's talking!
We all want to get signed, don't we?
Obviously.
To be honest with you guys, I think this is going to be my last chance.
To go pro, at least.
Hmm.
Nah, come on, you're exaggerating.
Mine too.
I'm not dumb.
I know what level I'm at.
We've got to ace this if we want to make the team.
And that won't be easy.
My dudes, we're the losers on the field.
I don't want to join my high school soccer team, play three years, and then ditch it, like everyone else.
That's where we're at.
But that's not where I want to be.
So I'm going to change it, no matter what it takes.
Of course, Tajibana doesn't have to worry about any of that, since he's going to get promoted to his club's youth team regardless.
Yeah, right.
Sorry.
Haven't improved as a player in quite a while.
The home club I grew up in isn't exciting or challenging at all anymore.
I'm just losing my competitive edge in general.
It's fine.
I came here today to try snapping myself out of it.
If I don't go pro, my life's over.
I'm done.
That's wild.
I've never given much thought to whether or not I'll go pro.
I play because I love the game, that's all.
You guys are the best.
I mean that.
I've never played at such a high level in my entire life.
I don't see a single loser on this team.
And I'm not smart enough to lie to you.
What I'm saying is legit.
You're all awesome.
I can't wait to play soccer with you.
Sorry for the wait.
Here are your final opponents.
Allow me to introduce...
The Tokyo City Espirion Youth Team.
See you on the field.
Have a good match.
What's that manager thinking?
It's so messed up.
What?
Oh, seriously?
Hey!
What do you think you're doing, huh?
Really?
These guys are on a whole other level of physique and skills.
It's not fair.
How are we supposed to showcase our skills against them?
You're saying you can't play against players who are stronger than you?
The fact is, you're trying to prove that you deserve to be one of them.
This is the perfect chance to do just that.
So show us what you got.
It makes a lot of sense if you think about it.
This is ridiculous.
I mean, get real.
Babies.
So this is the Espirion Youth, huh?
I saw them play in the final of last year's J Youth Cup.
The skill on display was beyond anything I was expecting.
It was way above the level of regular high school soccer.
I have dreamt for so long to one day play soccer on that level.
I have an ambition, you see.
Oh.
And one more thing.
At some point during the game, I'll have something to tell you all.
It won't be an instruction or anything like that, but I expect your full attention.
The crowd is still buzzing.
It's hard to concentrate.
Let's win this!
Win.
Howie's right, you guys.
We can win this.
I've seen a bunch of their members in the Under-15 League,
and most of them are first years in high school.
And that means they're only one year above us.
So I believe we have a better chance than we thought.
Fukuda.
What's up, Akutsu?
I want to play.
Is it possible for you to put me on the team?
Where's this coming from?
Exactly!
So quit crying!
We're gonna beat those jerkwads, and then they'll have no excuse!
They'll have to sign all of us up!
There seems to be a misunderstanding.
I don't think you really get who we are, do you?
Our best bet is a 3-5-2 formation.
Let's have Aoi and Kaneda as the two up front.
I can play in the pocket.
Aoi.
Can I play on the right?
Sure!
Whatever you want!
Hasegawa is holding midfielder.
That cool?
You all good with me commanding the back line?
That's great.
I'd like the defenders to limit how much they go forward,
and just focus on defense.
Sound good?
Aw, yeah!
Let's get to it!
Are they still working out their plan?
Come on, hurry it up!
Hey, man!
What happened to your cleats?
Um, well...
I guess they're, um...
They might be a little well-worn,
but I'm a sucker for comfort.
What can I say?
Akutsu, first year of Asperion youth.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Ashito Aoi, from Ehime.
Okay, back at ya.
So polite and well-mannered.
Dang, I always pictured the youth team as elite.
And I was right.
What?
No way.
There's a huge blank space all of a sudden.
Is it a trap?
Aw, man.
Otomo!
Hey!
No pressure, no marking.
I'm slicing through them like butter.
Aoi!
Hm?
Ah!
That was so close!
Did you see that?
It only took three of them to break through their line.
Otomo!
He passed it in behind them again!
Another close one!
Do you even know how to play this game?
How embarrassing!
The youth team is supposed to be their inspiration!
You're losing to the losers!
Get it together!
Are you okay?
I got excited and gave myself a nosebleed.
Are they trying to go easy on us?
No way.
What do you think?
Are those the benchwarmers?
Does that work?
Yep.
No problem.
Great.
Nice.
That was faster than I thought.
They might play at a pro level, but they're not doing so hot today.
Let's do this!
Go, number 10!
Breakthrough down the wing!
Only one defender to beat.
If I can get past him, I'll be right at the goal.
I can use that first touch technique that the old man taught me.
I'll land the ball right there.
And he won't have any time to react.
No!
He got back already!
Don't just stand there!
Go and get the ball!
Their passes are so accurate!
Unbelievable!
They're moving the ball around with only one touch passes!
And barely any dribbling!
Awesome, huh?
I bet you're a little lost since you don't play, though.
One touch passing.
Pass the ball with a single touch.
No trapping it or dribbling first.
If they do it right, they can bear down on the other team's goal really fast.
However, this style of play requires everyone involved to have exceptional passing, positioning, and the ability to calculate where the space will be.
Meaning, in order to execute it successfully, all 11 of them must share a perfect mental map of the route the ball's going to take.
That's unbelievable!
Snap out of it, you idiot!
Do you like getting outplayed like this?
Because I sure as hell don't!
For real this time!
Take it down, End!
That's it for the first half!
This kind of thing doesn't happen in real life.
I took the ball down and kicked it as soon as it landed?
That means he knew exactly where I was trying to place it the entire time.
Who is this guy?
Hey, so about your cleats.
Is it because you can't afford new ones?
What's the big deal if I can't?
I heard you traveled a long way.
Must have been pretty expensive.
Who paid for your trip?
Something's out there for you, so go find it.
It's sad to see such a lack of talent.
Pathetic, really.
I'm not talking about you.
I mean the kids around you.
Talentless losers talking about how hard this is for them.
That's not going to make any friends out here.
All you want to do is have fun playing soccer, right?
Go home.
We don't need that trash.
This isn't some little playground, kid.
Akutsu, you weren't running your mouth again, were you?
I don't get it.
Why didn't they do that one-touch passing from the start?
I wonder if they did it just to mock us.
Or maybe they were just showing off for the crowd.
Hmm.
It was pretty amazing, though.
Come on, Lee.
Hasegawa!
What are you all doing?
You want to join this meeting or what?
Oh, hey.
I haven't seen you guys since Inner High.
Eisuku Otomo.
You guys remember me?
If you think you can put your skills to full use today,
then we might not all have to go home.
I sure don't want it to end like this.
Do you?
Get that thing away from me!
What are you doing?
Nobody asked you to come and play nurse!
Don't underestimate me just because I'm pretty.
I know what I'm doing.
Stopping nosebleeds is super easy.
Who the heck is she supposed to be again?
She said something about being the old man's sister before.
That's kind of weird.
Pathetic, really.
I mean the kids around you.
Whoa!
You need to hold still!
You're too close!
Personal space, man!
That's Akutsu.
Is he bothering you?
I don't get what his problem is.
Scary, isn't he?
There are plenty of snobby elite-level players here.
He's definitely the worst.
And he's still a first-year, but he's already a starter.
Another thing?
He's the only member who made it in through last year's tryouts.
He was in the same position I am now.
Who is he to say if I have talent or not?
He's gonna regret that stupid punk.
Come on!
Second half's starting and I want us to pass!
Let's show them all how bad we can be!
You got this!
Wow.
That huddle looks a lot bigger than it did before.
That was like running into an iron wall!
This guy's core strength is crazy!
We're five minutes into the second half.
They really haven't done anything difficult like the one-touch passing from the first half.
They're keeping it simple.
Or not.
The youth team has some really talented players!
What the heck?
Is this real life?
It's like they're totally different players than they were at the start of the game!
Get over here!
Back to me!
You and I!
Come on, you guys!
Play on!
That Kaneda's kind of a hothead, don't you think?
Corner kick!
Nice stop, Koly!
Great job!
It's shocking how useless you all are.
All of a sudden you know how to play?
Dude, what's that supposed to prove?
It took us a while to warm up, I guess.
Hey, before the second half kicked off, you were all standing in a circle and clapping.
What was that about?
Aren't you guys all here to compete against each other?
Vomit.
Is talking trash like that how you managed to pass last year's tryouts?
Makes sense now.
Hmm?
You do you.
But I don't have to be a douchebag in order to get in.
Hey, you guys!
Quit pouting or I'm gonna spit!
It's a set play!
We gotta defend!
Who are you marking, huh?
Him?
Or him?
Um, we don't know.
After that, I'll go score some goals!
I need your help, alright?
No matter where I am on the field, I need you to get the ball to me!
Hey, you guys!
Owie's got a point!
We knew the youth team would be strong!
We were bound to give up a few goals!
Yeah!
We gotta stay focused on playing our best game!
Let's do it!
It's not over till it's over!
Hmm.
Owie!
Over there!
Clear it!
Yeah!
I swear, I didn't mean it!
I just lost my balance in midair!
I'm so sorry!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm great.
Can you move?
Let's get you off the field.
I could use a little help getting up here.
Do you mind?
I don't have time to be lying around.
We've got a game to finish, right?
Hey, are you sure you're okay, Owie?
Come over to the sidelines so I can take a look!
I don't need that.
I just need to score goals.
Please.
I can't let it end like this.
I need to stay.
I can't go back home now!
Dude, you actually think we let you leave before getting a chance to show you up?
No way!
Are you kidding?
Hey, Fukuda, wait!
Are you going to tell them?
You think now's the best time?
Now's as good a time as any, Nozomi.
Uh, there's something you should know.
During this game, I purposefully handicapped the youth team.
With the exception of the goalie, everyone's playing a position they've never played before.
So, you haven't played them at their best.
Next time on Awashi, Rope.